

ABOUT ME

Cyber Security enthusiast with 7+ years of experience as System Administration and Desktop Supporting Positions in busy corporate environment and Government Sectors, seeks for a Position in Cybersecurity domain where I could utilize my skills, experience and expertise towards the development and achieving the goals of the organization.

CONTACT

+91 7025 223 358

+91 8714 256 256



manoos.arun@gmail.com



Wayanad, Kerala, India



www.linkedin.com/in/arun-na

EDUCATION

2013 - 2016 BSC COMPUTER SCIENCE BHARATHIAR UNIVERSITY | COIMBATORE

2007-2010 **DIPLOMA IN ELECTRONICS ENGINEERING** GOVT POLY TECHNIC COLLEGE | MEPPADI

TECHNICAL TOOLS

- Nessus
- Burp suite
- Nmap
- Wireshark
- Metasploit

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH & MALAYALAM

ARUN N A



WORK EXPERIENCE

ASSISTANT SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR | C-DIT | TRIVANDRUM

MAR 2019 - Present

Conduct Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Testing of networks, web applications, mobile applications, desktop clients individually using automated and manual approach. Using tools such as Metasploit, Nessus, Burp suite. Responsible for the timely and 100% delivery of the entire Scope of work at the respective MVD office, Responsible for routine maintenance activities such as Monitoring, installation, integration, configuration, and maintenance of the IT system for 0% downtime

SYSTEM ASSISTANT | DISTRICT & SESSIONS COURT | KALPETTA FEB 2014 - MAR 2019

E-court Project, High court of Kerala under organizations like IHRD Cochin, IHRD Trivandrum, C-DIT Trivandrum and CMC limited a Tata Group, Chennai. Managing the entire District for the implementation of e-courts project. Coordinating survey for the installation of the e-court project under the High Court of Kerala.

DESKTOP ENGINEER L1 | TRICHUR COMPUTER CENTRE PVT LTD | KERALA SEP 2013 - FEB 2014

Give permanent Fix to the Desktop, Printer problems, and basic LAN & server support issues. Call Closure within Norms - Remote / On Site and Follow the Checklist(s) and Standard Process.

CUSTOMER SERVICE ENGINEER | EXCEL INFOTECH PVT LTD | COCHIN JAN 2012- JAN 2013

Resolving network issues, configuring operating systems and using remote desktop connections to provide immediate support. Installation and Configuration of Hardware and Software.

CERTIFICATIONS

CERTIFIED ETHICAL HACKER V11 - ECC4672095813 **CERTIFIED PENETRATION TESTER - RTHAKCHCPT254**

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Vulnerability Assessment & Penetration Testing
- Overview of Application Security
- Web Application Security Testing
- ➤ Basic knowledge in Network Vulnerability Scans
- ➤ Knowledge of OWASP top 10 Vulnerabilities
- ➤ Knowledge of TCP/IP and other application and Network protocols
- Operating Systems: Windows, Unix/Linux
- > Hands on experience of using Kali Linux